Guide to the Andrews Memorial Bookplate Collection of Irene D. Andrews Pace (School and College Bookplates)
Yale University Arts Library
- Bookplates
  - U – Y, undated (Box 5, Folder 29-36)
    - Yale University Library, New Haven, CT, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
      Armin Hemberger, artist
    - Yallourn Technical School, Monash University, Victoria, Australia, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
      Th. Broekstra, artist
  - Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Unknown school, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Unknown school, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
      Esdall, artist; Barralet, artist
    - Unknown school, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
      A. Johnson, artist